# Cindy Le

Mobile: 0468 627 647

Email: c.indle091@gmail.com

LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/cindyle09/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/cindyle09/</a>

#### **Professional Profile**

Currently a third-year Bachelor of Information Technology (Software Development) student with a variety of skills and interpersonal and communication attributes developed through employment and work experience involved in team-orientated environments.

Well-developed demeanour to remain calm and methodical throughout encounters with any situation at hand. Demonstrated great empathy, patience, and independence in maintaining a positive attitude to strive towards further developing my knowledge in my chosen field.

## Key Skills / Skills Summary

- Efficiently worked in teams with a high degree of responsibility, team-building skills, and good work ethic
- Strong knowledge and skills in software development gained through tertiary study and personal work/interest
- Well-developed interpersonal skills such as communication and patience gained through various experiences involving work experience, extra-curricular activities and so forth
- Articulate in active listening skills to understand and comprehend the speaker

## **Education / Qualifications**

# Bachelor of Information Technology (Software Development)

2020 - Current

University of South Australia

- GPA 6.53/7
- Expected completion by November 2022

Year 12 Graduate St Dominic's Priory College

2017

Microsoft Certified: Azure Fundamentals (AZ-900)

2022

# Significant Achievements / Highlights / Skillsets

IT Skills Front-end Development: JavaScript, React, Vue, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap,

TypeScript

**Back-end Development:** Python, Java, .NET Framework

**Testing:** Cypress, Python

Databases: MySQL, MongoDB

IT Skills Collaboration Tools: Microsoft Azure, GitLab, GitHub, JIRA, Trello,

IDEs: Visual Studio, Visual Studio Code, Eclipse

Design Tools: Figma, Framer, Adobe InDesign, Illustrator,

Photoshop, XD, Premier Pro

Awards University of South Australia Chancellor's Letters of Commendation 2021

University of South Australia STEM University Merit Award 2020

Year 12 Merit Subject Award for Design and Technology 2017

## **Employment History**

# Junior React Developer/Intern PwC

2022 - Current

- Junior Developer of PwC's Adelaide Skills Service Hub's Cloud/React Team
- Developed automated UAT smoke testing for current project engagement, and closely collaborated with other developers with identifying any bugs
- Maintaining quality assurance of the application
- Supported project's Business Analysts documenting bug reproduction of the current version of the application
- Engaged in learning a new testing framework (Cypress) for current project engagement

PASS Leader 2021 - Current

University of South Australia

- Serving as a peer facilitator for students at University of South Australia
- Role is to model and help promote and encourage effective study behaviour to students
- To be able to facilitate PASS sessions that involve combining study skills with key course content and to integrate how and what to learn

# University Projects / Placements / Extra-curricular

#### Tax Automate Platform V3

2022

Internal Project (PwC)

Enhancing V2 of PwC's Tax Automate Platform's features to further increase its scalability and functionality to create an even better and more efficient end-user experience to manage and automate income tax compliance and reporting processes.

• Role: Test Automator

• Testing framework: Cypress

Collaboration Tools: Microsoft Azure

Web development 2022

Personal Project

Developed an online portfolio by creating an interactive webpage to share a bit about the developer and their work that they have been involved in.

Role: Front-end developer

Languages: TypeScript, React, CSS

• Tools: Vitejs, Figma

Source Code: GitHub

Link to Webpage

## Covid Check-In Application

2021

**University Project** 

Developed a web application in a team to address a problem for a real-world client – creating a new solution for COVID tracing to enhance and simply user experience.

• Role: Front-end Developer and Designer

Languages: TypeScript, React, CSS

Database: MongoDB

• Collaboration Tools: GitHub, JIRA, Framer

Source Code: GitHub

UniSA UniMentor 2021

• Provide students ongoing support and become an individual that can be relied on (helping students transition into tertiary studies)

- Weekly contact with mentees to offer timely advice and information
- To answer questions/queries as well as provide continual advice and support throughout the program

### Referees

### Hannah Webber

Academic Services Officer – UniSA STEM

Telephone: +61 8 8302 5231

Email: hannah.webber@unisa.edu.au

### Nicole Vincent

Project Officer – Accredited PASS Supervisor

Telephone: +61 8302 7219 Email: pass@unisa.edu.au

# Zisis Katsavelis

Manager – PwC

Telephone: +61 414 825 285 Email: <u>zisis.katsavelis@pwc.com</u>